dropkaffe.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy - Goodness! Beverages

#### Privacy Policy:

Please read this privacy policy before using the site [http://www.drinkgoodness.com](http://www.paperboatdrinks.com/) or submitting any personal information.

Your privacy is important to DropKaffe. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that DropKaffe collects, and the ways in which DropKaffe uses that personal information.

By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. DropKaffe Food & Beverages Pvt. Ltd. reserves the right to change this policy without prior notice. The policy will be updated on this website before it gets effective.

DropKaffe Food & Beverages Pvt. Ltd. (“Company,” “we”, “us”, “our” or “DropKaffe”, “Oh My Goodness”) is the sole owner of the information collected on all DropKaffe Websites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

We strive to ensure the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our collection of information policies.

#### Note:

This privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of the then current policies.

By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not choose to accept these terms, please do not use this website.

By using this Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions.

#### Personal information collection

DropKaffe may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website
  * information about transactions carried out over this website
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to DropKaffe.

If you choose to make a purchase from our site, we may collect information pertaining to your buying behaviour.

The information we collect includes, but is not limited to: Name, Date of Birth, E-mail Address, Billing Address, Shipping Address, Phone/Mobile number, Recipient’s Phone/Mobile number.

This information is necessary for us to recognize you as a registered customer and to fulfil the orders you place with us. Storing this information means you do not need to re-enter these details each time you shop. The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. The information we collect will be used to contact consumers in future, for designing consumer surveys, contests and is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agencies and partners (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

#### Using personal information

DropKaffe collects and stores all personally identifiable information which you provide. This information is used by us to ensure efficient use of our website and highly customized shopping experience.

DropKaffe may use your personal information to:

  * administer and operate this website
  * personalize and improve you experience on this website
  * enable your access to and use of the website services
  * publish information about you on the website
  * send to you and/or the identified recipient(s) the products that you purchase
  * supply to you and/or the identified recipient(s) services that you purchase
  * send to you statements and invoices
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you relevant marketing communications

If you choose to upload data from Facebook or Instagram, we do not collect your usernames and passwords from Facebook or Instagram.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

DropKaffe may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

DropKaffe may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process to defend its legal rights. DropKaffe may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms and Conditions or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

#### Communications from the Site

#### _Special Offers and Updates_

We may occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. We present the option not to receive these types of communications.

#### _Press Releases and Newsletters_

If you request to receive our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send these documents to you. Please contact us if you wish to be removed from this mailing list.

#### _Service-related Announcements_

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email advising you of this.

#### Cookies

Hector Beverages uses cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.

#### No Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

DropKaffe does not use clear gifs (I.e. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) in our HTML-based emails.

Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users and to let companies know which emails recipients have opened, allowing them to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of their online marketing campaigns. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

#### Links to Other Sites

This website may contain links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. DropKaffe is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites

#### Securing your data

DropKaffe will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent unauthorised access, loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

DropKaffe will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers or secure servers of its third-party affiliates. We do not use any encryption on our forms, as we do not collect credit card numbers, social security numbers or any other sensitive information that can be used in identity theft.

#### Cross-border data transfers

Information that DropKaffe collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which DropKaffe operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website may be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

#### Business Transitions

In the event DropKaffe goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will be among the assets transferred.

#### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If DropKaffe decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review this page periodically. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page
